Review exercise E, Two- and Three-Word Set Phrases. You should be pretty familiar
with the idea of a set phrase by now. The next step is when you have more components
that link together to form a new thing, a three-word set phrase. Combine three
things, finger plus nail plus clipper. Leave the stress on the first word,
fingernail clipper. Although you're now using three words, they still mean one new
thing. The next thing is using the word combinations from the previous exercises. One, it's a
fingernail. It's a fingernail clipper. Two, it's a pancake. It's a pancake shop.
Three, it's a hot tub. It's a hot tub maker. Four, it's a hard drive. It's a
hard drive holder. Five, it's the backbone. It's a backbone massage. It's a
playing card. It's a playing card rack. Seven. It's a spotlight. It's a spotlight
stand. Eight. It's a phone book. It's a phone book listing.